I am your Suraj, first of all, once half
almond outlook and half a minute good morning
good morning ji, so all the news UP
President and there was a correction of two-three days,
after that there is extra oil, but still I will ask some
questions here,
while I know that the market quality
number of 50,000 will definitely be seen that here
Ayush hunger profit hand look into correction
to my WhatsApp specific, Intex
can be a little bit different vehicles
master good news prices for me
activate like it will be aluminum
profit booking noble on this matter this question is also in the mind
of the village directly
practical dollar and if something comes from there on dollar
why then Indian is also harmful
for remarks ignoring his profit booking
which is according to love and authority, this office
mature response has been wasted with good
qualities to give
loot number will give update in stock market
ji had done and release music for children's call
from Dual app I had
said Bandhan Bank very loudly Laxman 56
58 lakhs in that 6767 before the science results
any problem rest Jatin liked it
you will also remember 35 last started
don't promise there Tata Power Maruti has become
book profit there PNB Status has become
book profit there and
what about Godrej Properties 1429 but that is still
MS Word will be done on 15 ghat now if you say
my friend that you have one condition then I will
start after which Singh is also an oil
so let's start first two times like this a so
first brother if Tata Consumer Fighting
Papa Aaj Tak tumor scheduled van vik
a little profit-taking will come in the bank
by keeping a stoploss of phase Shyam Tata Sons *
constipation and result Fernandez was the favorite
only coming in the soil also Sudevi a
rating a Baahubali etc decorate
Balkrishna Industries 1650 take in childhood
stoploss of 1630 is 1750 1725 1740
creates and in waste if  High or low bid
foiled in Krishna looking very wick and
displayed remotely on insurance 2018 live
ID number find 1465 beautiful 1495
browser Chrome target is one while will
give you apk file MS Word 2003 things
are perfect Tata Sons all the
staff selection of Tata Group and
also in the stocks related to peace mission this cancer in 593 595 range
582 582 custom hair pores Pankaj's
teeth Bal Krishna interesting here
one hour retires from all are strong
in the range of 1655 will do 1632 place top
floor and above 1725 1740 1725 1740 2016
Secretary stoploss shot has to be done ICICI
Lombard 1465 01604
16 inches on the occasion of 70's festival and jaundice 1465 brother 1495
1495 stop its level is likely to fall for 14 years
its 1200  This baton fix to give our blood